[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At the end of Return of the Jedi, Darth Vader gets redeemed by reverting back to his former self.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this novel, set during WWII, Sue Ann Duckett is one of the ward nurses in the hospital where Yossarian gets treated, and later starts a relationship with him.", "correct_answer": "Catch-22", "incorrect_answers": ["Slaughterhouse-Five", "One Flew Over the Cuckoos Nest", "Cats Cradle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This creature belongs to the rodent family and is covered in sharp spines or quills.", "correct_answer": "Porcupine", "incorrect_answers": ["Nutria", "Armadillo", "Kiwi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which medical term refers to the crackling sound, produced when two rough surfaces in the human body come into contact?", "correct_answer": "Crepitus", "incorrect_answers": ["Bunion", "Exostosis", "Osteoporosis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What chemical is used to trigger the ripening of tomatoes that have been picked unripe?", "correct_answer": "Ethylene", "incorrect_answers": ["Vitamin A", "Lycopene", "Glucose"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "King Edward VIII abdicated the English throne for the woman I love. He later became the Gouverneur of what land ?", "correct_answer": "The  Bahamas", "incorrect_answers": ["Fiji", "Jamaica", "Barbados"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Morgan Freeman movie won Best Picture at the 62nd annual Academy Awards?", "correct_answer": "Driving Miss Daisy", "incorrect_answers": ["Outbreak", "Unforgiven", "Glory"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Comparing a newborn babys skeletal system to an adults skeletal system, we will find out that the baby has about 60 bones more that the already completely developed person.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the most common reason for airplane incidents?", "correct_answer": "Human error", "incorrect_answers": ["Overload", "Equipment malfunction", "Weather conditions"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What word/phrase did the Waco Kid say that he started to hear in his sleep in the movie Blazing Saddles?", "correct_answer": "Draw", "incorrect_answers": ["Youre Dead", "Stick Em Up", "Reach for It  Mister"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What property of light might change its value when a beam of light crosses the border between vacuum and another medium or between two different media?", "correct_answer": "The wavelength", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "The polarization", "The intensity"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Located in the Northwest Territories, what lake empties into the Mackenzie River and is considered the largest lake that is entirely within Canada?", "correct_answer": "Great Bear Lake", "incorrect_answers": ["Lake Huron", "Lake Superior", "Great Slave Lake"]}]